<?xml version="1.0"?>
<bugs date="7.2.2007">
  <bug>
    <title>
Too many template conflict / competition messages
</title>
    <severity>Medium</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <description>
There are too many messages about competition between templates.
<ul><li>Each competing pair is reported twice (x with y and y with z)</li><li>Competing pairs that are a consequence of stylesheet simplification (does that exist??) should not be reported.</li></ul>
A proper fix requires a better framework for competition analysis
than just logging each case as it is discovered.
</description>
    <research-log>
      <log-entry>Blah</log-entry>
    </research-log>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Does NS URI work for DTD?
</title>
    <severity>High</severity>
    <status>Closed</status>
    <reproducability>
ObservedIncident
</reproducability>
    <description>
In the purchaseorder2invoice democase, try using the DTD instead of the RNG on the output side.
Specify the correct namespace URI, 'invoice'.
The validator seems not to get the namespace right.
</description>
    <research-log>
      <log-entry>It might have been the radio button gone forgotten. The value comes through OK _when_ the
      radio button is selected.</log-entry>
    </research-log>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
JS bugs in BRICS production - edit page
</title>
    <severity>Medium</severity>
    <status>Closed</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
MSIE 6
</environment>
    <description>
The line and column number computation or display JS on the edit pages does not work.
Seems OK in Mozilla.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Too many options appear in input schema diagnostics view
</title>
    <severity>Low</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
After clicking update in the input diagnostics view, FOUR checkboxes
appear. The three of them are irrelevant and should not appear.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Download of input schema diagnostics fails
</title>
    <severity>Low</severity>
    <status>Closed</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
Clicking download in the input schema diagnostics causes a JSP exception.

org.apache.jasper.JasperException: /XMLDownload.jspx(7,77) According to TLD or attribute directive in tag file, attribute items does not accept any expressions
	org.apache.jasper.servlet.JspServletWrapper.handleJspException(JspServletWrapper.java:510)
	org.apache.jasper.servlet.JspServletWrapper.service(JspServletWrapper.java:375)
	org.apache.jasper.servlet.JspServlet.serviceJspFile(JspServlet.java:314)
	org.apache.jasper.servlet.JspServlet.service(JspServlet.java:264)
	javax.servlet.http.HttpServlet.service(HttpServlet.java:802)

</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Validator / session threads get into a messy state when users browse among democases
</title>
    <severity>Critical</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
When the user browses back and forth between democases, all
sorts of strange things happen to the session state.
That is not good for confidence.
An immediate solution is to ask users to shut down their browser
between each democase. A better solution hopefully is found.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Missing JS auto-selection of string input radio button
</title>
    <severity>Low</severity>
    <status>Closed</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
When a stylesheet module or a schema is uploaded, there is JS functionality
that automatically switches to the BrowseFile / URL / TEXT input type
used by the user.
This functionality is missing for text inputs (namespace URI and root
element name).
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Gateway timeout message
</title>
    <severity>Medium</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
When a large / heavy validation case is run, the
BRICS apache server comes up with some kind of gateway
timeout message, even though the validator is still running.
Could the server timeout be extended?
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Output schema root element for XSD must be manually
inputtable also when using Schematools-style output
schema construction
</title>
    <severity>Medium</severity>
    <status>Closed</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
The format of the output schema root element name (given by the user / environment)
is different in Schematools from in the XSLV: Schematools uses
Clark form, while the dongfang stuff uses plain names.
<br/>
A feature must be provided for the user to give a root element name
manually when Schematools constructs the output schema (see .......).
Right now that is only possible when the output schema is constructed
in the dongfang identity-transform-input way.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
The enabled=true/false attribute in the triple element should be respected 
in the on-line democase code
</title>
    <severity>Low</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
Instead of having to edit jsp's to enable or disable demo cases,
the already existing enabled attribute on the triple.xml's triple
element should be used.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Schematools could use some kind of settable resolution context...
</title>
    <severity>Low</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
...for pulling in included or imported resources referred by URIs in another way than just resolving the URI.
Without that, includes in xsds won't work so well.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
What ever happened to schema validation...
</title>
    <severity>High</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
... of the provided XSLT stylesheets and schemas?
If enabling it right now (ModelConfiguration.java), XSLV goes dead in some mysterious way.
</description>
  </bug>
  <bug>
    <title>
Validation dies in some large cases
</title>
    <severity>High</severity>
    <status>Open</status>
    <reproducability>
Reproduceable
</reproducability>
    <environment>
Any
</environment>
    <description>
Validation terminates in some funny way with for example the dsd2xhtml case, without a result.
Is that really a feature (time out)?
</description>
  </bug>
</bugs>
